{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"9.0.2","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":7104,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":4,"width":1024,"height":627,"responsive":false,"scalable":true,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"Image_53","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_53","roles":{}},{"id":"si10858","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"SmartShape_27","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_27","title":"Begin Assessment ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11153","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Begin Assessment ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11165","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Begin Assessment ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10958","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10947","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10967","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Path To Calculus ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10971","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide4528","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Path To Calculus Assesment","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_53","si10858","SmartShape_27","si11153","si11165","si10958","si10947","si10967","si10971"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":6834},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4528"}}},{"id":"si10553","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide9390q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10575","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide9390q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9529","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si9449","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Question1 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9456","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A particle moves along the x-axis. The velocity of the particle at time t is 6t - t2. What is the total distance traveled by the particle from time t = 0 to t = 3 ? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9471","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9475","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"  3 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9471_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"  3\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si9482","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9486","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"  6  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9482_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"  6\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10290","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10294","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"  9 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10290_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"  9\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10305","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10309","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"  18 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10305_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"  18\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si10602","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10606","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"  27 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10602_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"  27\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si9533","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide9390q0","for":"Slide9390q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9390","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si10553","si10575","si9449","si9456","si9475","si9486","si10294","si10309","si10606","si9533"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9390"},"question":{"interactionId":"9436","quizId":377,"title":"Question1\r","text":"A particle moves along the x-axis. The velocity of the particle at time t is 6t - t2. What is the total distance traveled by the particle from time t = 0 to t = 3 ?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si11785","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11784q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11794","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11784q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11731","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_38","roles":{}},{"id":"si11647","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_10","title":"Question2 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11659","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_11","title":"If f(x)=7x-3+lnx,then f’(1)=? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11703","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_34","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11707","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_35","title":"  4 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11703_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"22","roles":{"answer":{"title":"  4\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11714","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_36","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11718","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_37","title":"  5 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11714_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"24","roles":{"answer":{"title":"  5\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11812","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11816","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"  6 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11812_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"  6\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11827","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11831","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"  7 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11827_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"  7\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11842","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11846","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"  8 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11842_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"  8\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si11763","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide11784q1","for":"Slide11784q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11850","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide11784q1","for":"Slide11784q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11864","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide11784q1","for":"Slide11784q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11878","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Skip ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide11784q1","for":"Slide11784q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide11784","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si11785","si11794","si11647","si11659","si11707","si11718","si11816","si11831","si11846","si11763","si11850","si11864","si11878"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide11784"},"question":{"interactionId":"11633","quizId":377,"title":"Question2\r","text":"If f(x)=7x-3+lnx,then f’(1)=?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["E"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si9230","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9241","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9274","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si9282","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si9290","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si9298","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si9306","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si9314","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si9263","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9270","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You Scored: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9278","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Maximum Score: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9286","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9294","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9302","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Accuracy: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9310","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Attempts: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9318","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si9322","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9336","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Retake Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"retake","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9220","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9220"}}},{"id":"Pool421","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":421,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"PerfectEd-Assessment-vs1","class":"project","title":"PerfectEd-Assessment-vs1","children":["Slide4528","Slide9390","Slide11784","Slide9220"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":377,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":false,"questions":["Slide9390q0","Slide11784q1"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":20,"passScore":16}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":false,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide4528","title":"Path To Calculus Assesment"},{"id":"Slide9390","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide11784","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide9220","title":"Slide 4"}]}